(Amy:)of you even going to Mars
are incredibly small,
(Amy:)but it still hurts
that you would volunteer
(Amy:)for something that would
take you away from me forever.
(Sheldon:)So you're saying you
wouldn't leave me
(Sheldon:)for the chance to be
one of the first humans
(Sheldon:)to colonize
another planet?
(Amy:)I would at least mention it
(Amy:)before filling out
the application.
(Sheldon:)Huh, that's exactly what
Leonard, Wolowitz, Koothrappali,
(Sheldon:)Bernadette and
Penny said.
(Amy:)And who says
you could even survive
(Amy:)an interplanetary
mission, anyway?
(Amy:)You could barely survive
a tiny turtle bite.
(Sheldon:)First of all, this...
(Sheldon:)has only made me stronger.
(Sheldon:)But beyond that, all I did
(Sheldon:)was fill out an application.
(Amy:)You know what?
(Amy:)Go to Mars, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Is there anything I can
do to cheer you up?
(Amy:)No. Forget it.
What if I play the Star Trek
theme on my nose?
(Amy:)Please don't.
(humming the Star Trek theme)